Guide to the Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York records, 1830-1980
Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York records, 1830-1980
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York records, 1830-1980.
3780
Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York.
1.1 cubic ft.
Minutes, records, photocopies, rosters, microfilm
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York, a Dutch Reformed church (formerly the Reformed Dutch Church of Farmerville, New York), including minutes, membership lists, and records of baptisms and marriages.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Reformed Church of Interlaken, New York.; Reformed Church in America.
Subjects:
Dutch Reformed Church.
Places:
Farmerville (N.Y.).; Interlaken (N.Y.).; Seneca County (N.Y.).
Form and Genre Terms:
Minute books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Book 1, 1830-1838
  - Membership, pages 3-8 (Box 1)
  - Minutes of Consistory, pages 1, 2, 9-34 (Box 1)
  - Record of Baptisms and Marriages, back of book (Box 1)
- Book 2, 1838-1905
  - Membership, pages 1-8, 1838-1869 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, pages 19-end, 1838-1905 (Box 1)
  - Record of Baptisms and Marriages, back of book (Box 1)
- Book 3, 1878-1918
  - Church Members, pages 1-49 (Box 2)
  - Marriages, pages 150-167 (Box 2)
  - Baptisms, pages 224-239 (Box 2)
- Book 4, 1905-1926
  - Minutes, pages 1-218 (Box 2)
  - A History of the Interlaken Reformed Church, 1830-1980, pub. 1980 by Maurice Patterson, et. al. (Box 2)
- Book 5
  - Minutes, Jan. 1927-Nov. 1946 (Box 3)
- Book 6
  - Minutes, Nov. 21, 1946-Dec. 1955 (Box 3)
- Book 7
  - Minutes, Feb. 1955-Mar. 1964 (Box 4)
- Book 8
  - Minutes, Aug. 1961-Dec. 1969 (Box 4)
- Book 9
  - Minutes, Jan. 1970-Dec. 1975 (Box 4)
- Book 10, 1925-1977
  - Members, Marriages, Baptisms (microfilm) (Reel 1)